Wake up, Costatas.
I'm awake.
I'm
very much wait.
Let me just make sure I did this.
I think I did.
Oh, by the way, I'm reading that book you recommended.
The 20 odd words that created the internet.
Yep.
Huh?
Yes, yes, that one.
Yeah, isn't it dry as fuck?
It's actually, well, I mean, I wouldn't say it's dry as fuck, but it is really good.
Yeah, I know, it's super interesting, but it's super dry.
It's like something.
I guess we're, okay, so I don't know what you mean by dry.
Maybe that's the problem.
I don't know.
I mean, it's not.
It's got, you know, no interesting prose or storyline to speak of.
I mean, it's just a long-form Wikipedia article, right?
Oh, yes, yes.
In that sense, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It reads very much like something a lawyer would write.
Yeah, I mean, and it is, right?
Like, I think it actually is from Barry.
He's a lawyer.
No, the author is a lawyer.
He makes that point quite clear.
As does his prose.
Oh, my God, his prose.
Yeah.
But it's super interesting to me because it's just, it's crazy all the stuff that went into the history of Section 230.
And what's really interesting, I guess, from my perspective is the fact that the book, like, so there's this meme on Facebook, right?
Among social media, especially some people whom I follow on social media.
They'll go, well, you know, there's no big company, no big internet companies in Europe.
And I'm like, yeah, but there's no big internet companies in Europe that just got sued by the federal government for harming young girls.
Okay, but we can always make more young girls.
Sorry.
You do realize, yes, young girls, right?
I'm terrible.
If it wasn't for the fact that we know who you are, we would be offended.
Yeah.
No, you know, I am a fan of move fast and break shit.
You know, I don't like stagnation.
This is not a statement.
This is actually not a statement of one is better than the other.
There was an explicit trade-off made.
Yeah.
Right.
Like, you could say the trade-off was literally that one.
In Europe, they decided that they would rather they've valued collective, let's call it certain, they value different things and say they had different outcomes.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, that's absolutely true.
It's what you prioritize for.
Right.
Okay.
Here's the summary of events according to Brewbarry.
Brewbarry, who's not with us today.
Of course, we're also missing a Vukradin.
Oh, didn't he?
Did he say he wasn't going to make it this week?
I forget.
I don't take notes.
I don't see anything there.
No, I thought he might have mentioned it in session.
I didn't see anything like that.
One of these days I'll stop being an old man going to bed at nine.
And you'll instead go to your coffin at night.
Yeah.
I did not make a funny picture yet for the session.
Oh, damn it.
What do we pay you for?
Portal runs the board laid bare, cooks better than anyone.
I have hidden from Soma's friend for years.
Her privacy never moved while the rest of the city doubled.
And that is because her supplier was never on the manifold in the first place.
I went into her kitchen with a Halbert in one arm and the dragon sword in the other and a story about needing a delivery partner.
The story did not work.
I'm getting inspired now.
Okay.
Petra was booking a man to play Vukradin's song under our band name every night.
She'd always disclose it was not him and she made money off him anyway.
He says, you got to send these out earlier than, you know, five minutes into the session.
I know, I know, I know.
I'm sorry, I thought I had done that.
I'm just looking.
I was like, Jesus, there's a lot here to scroll through.
And I'm like, I want to read it.
I just would have read it, you know, 30 minutes ago.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, that was my bad.
I felt bad.
I thought I'd sent it.
Yeah.
That's okay.
I am just.
Hey, you know, you're a service top.
It's fine.
Anyway, you'll figure out what you know where Section 230 got tested weirdly.
I love all the crazy history about how it was used.
It's basically, we've got to treat this like a bookstore.
A bookstore can't be held liable for everything.
You know, no, no, I mean, it's very fascinating to see how a set of decisions produced a set of outcomes.
Yeah.
Right.
And what's even more is the Telecommunications Decency Act had a lot of shit in it, and it all got paired back.
Like, the only thing that survived is like the 26 words that are worth keeping.
It's almost like the Anti-Communications Decency Act, or maybe the Wade-approved version of the Communications Decency Act.
Yeah, it's what we're talking about, Section 230.
Yeah.
You're no longer employed by Google, so you don't have to worry about legal consequences.
But the reason we're talking about it is because Wade recommended a book called The 26 Words That Change the Internet.
Created it.
The Created the Internet.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I thought it was, and I was telling him that I was reading it, and it's a superb book.
It is.
I've never found anything like it.
I've tried.
I don't know what it is about it, but it's just fantastic.
Let me send a note to Dave.
I don't know whether he's joining us.
26 Words is the name of the book.
26 Words that Created the Internet.
And it's just like 200 pages on Section 230.
200 pages on 26 words.
And it's a series of legal cases.
Essentially, it describes the origin of the law, right?
Where the law started.
It describes how the law came into existence, the set of legal challenges that were made against the laws, and Data City John Yes, and how those laws affect, how they evolved over time.
And it explains.
I'm not intimidated by legal stuff.
What?
Oh, no, it's not.
It's not intimidating.
It's very approachable.
That is a feature of me.
Yeah.
But it's a very easy, very easy read for how deep it goes into detail.
Like, I keep joking, it's a long form Wikipedia.
Yeah, man.
And it's very well written.
I was reading Don't Be Evil.
I will say it is a little bit less about Google, more about technology companies in general, and about her dating life.
Her dating life?
Dating life?
Who?
Claire Steepleton.
So this is a book by someone I knew at Google that was talking about her experience called Don't Be Evil.
And it is, yeah, it's been going around the circuit lately.
But I will say that there's a whole lot more dating, office dating going on than I have been aware of.
I mean, you're not supposed to be aware of it.
Unless you're a tremendous gossip.
His name is Bimbo.
I don't know why you keep writing Bimbo in here.
Hi, Dave.
Hey.
Vukradin's out today.
Yeah, he said he's got, I don't know, something.
He claimed he had some issue.
He actually didn't even say why.
He just said, no.
Are we going back to the old Brutish Brewbarry or we need to channel the new find Brewbarry?
I can do either.
He's a man of culture.
Like finely woven woolen robe.
Dude, he's still a man of the people.
Don't forget, he wears his armor, and on top he wears his bathrobe.
And underneath he wears a Hawaiian shirt.
I would think that it would get very dirty, the bathrobe.
But we already covered that in character.
He believes that that adds color and character to the bathrobe.
That's why you start with the red bathrobe.
All the blood just blends in.
It's brown and dirty all the time.
I mean, are you going to tell that?
Are you going to tell that to him?
No.
Is Vukradin going to tell Brewbarry that his clothes look awful?
I don't think Vukradin cares about such things.
Really?
No.
He's not a fashionista.
He cares about right and wrong and music.
So it has to vary on the performances.
Nope.
I guess Brewbarry is not on stage.
He's at the backstage or in the audience.
He's not on stage.
He's always in the audience cheering 10 out of 10.
I thought, wait, hold on.
I thought we said more cowbell.
He's the cowbell ringer.
Okay.
We were going to the sewers.
Was that the plan?
We're going to do that stakeout.
Oh, yeah.
We're going to do the stakeout.
Got to watch where that extra crate's getting off, too.
That's right.
Let's do it.
Okay, so I sent out a Brewbarry take on what's going on.
Had some funny moments.
My favorite one is:
nine crates go down that lane, eight go inside, one walks away on its own.
Someone stopped paying that gnome on purpose, and somebody is feeding him on purpose.
And either that is the same person or it is two.
And I find out which one tonight.
I am a barbarian, not a thief.
I do not work in the shadows, and I let my enemy know that I am there.
And yet tonight I go quiet because Lynn asked me to, and because Soma is already unhappy with me.
Poor Brewbarry.
I have a very high stealth if we need me to, if we need someone to do something stealthily.
I mean, you could tag along with a familiar ice on that.
Well, it's just telling you, you've got a plus nine with advantage.
So if it's necessary to have an actual character, yes.
Damn.
I didn't know Bard's got high stealth.
If you choose it.
Ah, yeah.
Got your feet.
I do have a plus five.
I have boots of Elven kind.
Ah, yeah.
I do have a plus five stealth.
Well, it's not plus nine, though.
I don't have your perception and all the other crazy things you have.
But you mean you're not what you're saying is you can walk past Valphine without her noticing.
I don't think anybody can.
I don't think anyone can do that.
Well, technically, my perception is only plus seven.
Right.
So yours is plus nine.
So depends on the roll, right?
Passive.
Passive self versus passive perception.
Is that a thing?
I think you roll against my passive.
Yes, I know.
I know.
It was a joke.
All right.
So where are we?
So when we last left our Noble Adventures, you were playing at the Common Cord.
Oh, right.
And we negotiated.
Yes.
What a good deal.
Yeah.
So Petra said it was given, you negotiated 500 gold pieces as a one-time payment for all the likenesses for your likeness.
Past and future.
Right.
Yes.
500 gold.
Performance in two days.
Yes, it's on the quest tracker.
Right, right.
So, so, so that you're also waiting for it to be 3 a.m.
before you head out to Broadlight Bear.
Caps Grace.
Yep.
On the quest tracker.
Right.
And so, and there's still the small matter of meeting Lord Nevermember, but you kind of he's Aldous hasn't contacted you about when exactly dinner is.
Is it Nevermember or Never Winter?
I'm kidding.
Never Ember.
Lord Never Ember.
Yes.
Never Ember.
It's never like a fire Ember.
Yes, I think it is.
Let me just go.
Now I got he's never flaming.
He keeps it on the DL.
Yeah, it's Lord Never Ember.
Yeah, that's.
I think Wade has it exactly right.
What was it?
Said he's never flaming.
He keeps it on the DL.
Yeah, never flaming.
The double entendres in these modules.
Ridiculous.
Okay, and Lord Never Ember.
Lord Never Flaming has a new drow advisor.
Wait, isn't that Valphine?
No.
Oh.
Oh, it's a rumor.
It's a rumor, and I suspect Valphine will know this advisor at dinner, but we will see.
I'm sorry, I lost track.
What do I do?
Lord, Never Ember.
Lord Never Flaming has a new Drow advisor that we will.
Oh, right, right, right.
Which we assume to be one of my siblings.
That is my guess, too.
Yes.
Yeah.
No, okay.
Everyone's related to everyone.
You know, I'm Greek, so this is kind of to be expected.
Okay.
Have we secured the capital for Brewbarry's bathrobe business, or is that still in progress?
I believe it's in progress.
What is in progress?
Securing money for the.
Oh, no, you've secured the money.
You've secured the money.
We have.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
Oh, but the cost of import is very high.
Right, because their shipping lanes are still shipping portals, whatever, are still hosed.
All right.
And House Margaster is in charge.
Of course they are.
But they deliver things on time and on schedule.
All right.
Let's head out to Lim's food deliveries and get there by 3 a.m.
And then we can cast whatever spells we need in order to be ready.
Dude.
Session book.
Never winter.
And the town is named Never Winter, right?
Yes.
Lord, Never Ember of Never Winter.
Never Ember of Never.
Ember.
Well, Ember and Winter are like opposites.
So there's that too.
That makes him a terrible Lord.
Yeah.
Well, at least he's under Mark Caster.
I'm kind of like curious: what's your name's take on House Margaster?
I mean, is she impressed with her control and what she's doing, or is she unimpressed?
I think Valphine is looking at Mark Caster as the competition.
Okay, that I understand.
I think there's going to have to be a moment where Lathander and Valphine may have to have a coming to Lathander.
Lathander's dead, dude.
Haven't you heard?
Lathander's death every night.
Hold on.
I need to get something to drink.
Okay.
We drove him to alcohol.
I think I have the.
And they say you can't kill gods.
I think I have the summary photo.
No.
I'll put it in the story so far.
Wandering torto tavern menu.
It's a torto soup.
Turtle for the turtle soup.
But it's turtles!
Soiled green.
Torturs.
No, it's not.
It's turtle soup, not made of turtles.
It's made of people.
I'm okay with that.
Crack nest menu.
The menu's a little pricey.
That doesn't seem very realistic.
We can adjust it.
Everything's 50 gold.
I think it's more like, you know, five silvers or something like that, or one silver.
I didn't know they had labeled exit signs in Never Winter.
Yeah.
Wow.
It's like OSHA compliant.
Is there a ramp or, you know, disable.
Yeah.
Is there an ADA in Feyrune?
All right.
Silas, do we need to catch up?
About what?
The picture.
Oh, sorry.
Tortle soup.
It's made with real humans.
Oh, good lord.
I'm terrified.
Oh, it's from Gary, not from me.
I can't laugh too loud.
It's turtle free.
But it's made of people.
Okay.
All right.
So.
Okay, so you're at the dive, right?
That used to throw you out unpaid.
It's the hardest ticket in Neverwinter.
And
that, you know, one of the locals is like talking that the court is unaffordable now and it's all due to Crowden.
And he sort of sees it, but kind of like talking about you without realizing you're standing within earshot of him.
I could tell him I'm planning on opening my own independent music studio.
And if he'd like to contribute to the charitable fund, that will speed the opening of a free, a low-cost, non-profit way to hear Lathander's death on a regular basis.
You'd make that offer.
Okay.
And spread the word.
Awesome.
We have, you know, there's a GoFundMe and, you know, QR code, Venmo, et cetera.
Right.
Sending stone in this case.
All the Feyrune equivalents.
Yes.
I take Google Pay, Apple Pay, Portal Pay.
p.m.
Yeah, Turtle Pay.
So one of the things you do learn is that as you're listening over here at the local bar is that the tide that goes through the sewers turns twice a day.
So you have to.
Tide in the sewers?
Yeah, from the river.
There's a tide in the sewers.
The river has a tide.
No, the town is right next to the sea.
The sea, the tides come in.
And so there's like two tides.
How many moons does this planet have?
You asked.
That's an easy question to answer.
Just the one?
It just rotates really or revolves really fast.
It has one moon named Saloon.
No, it actually has one.
Oh, Saloon.
Of course.
Yeah.
It's got Saloon and it's got the tears of Saloon.
Okay.
Oh, that's true.
So there should be a tidal effect from both moons.
No, because the other ones are actually asteroids.
Cluster of meters and asteroids.
They're not sufficiently gravitational.
Yes.
Is that what you're telling me?
Not really moons.
Yeah, they're just comets.
They're asteroids.
So the one moon then.
Oh, well, according to it, just so you know, experiences two high tides and two low tides each day.
There you go.
See, not one and one.
Too high and too low.
Yeah.
So what?
Jesus.
It's murder on trade.
Okay.
I should take effect underground too, right?
So it's a six-hour cycle.
Yeah.
And two daily high tides and two low tides.
So it's a six-hour cycle.
Yes.
So, yes.
Sorry, I should have.
High to low is three hours.
So, yes.
So there's this period of time when it's low tide weather.
No, high to low.
High to low is six hours.
Six.
All right.
So, yes.
So we want to be in the sewer for at low tide.
Yes, which just happens to be conveniently at three.
And we have about three hours, maybe four before things start to get really uncomfortable.
Exactly.
I mean, I can hang out underwater indefinitely.
Yes.
That's fine.
You can go for that.
Yes.
Okay.
So, you know, that's kind of like you overhear that amongst the discussion.
It's not directed at you.
All right.
Okay.
So I presume you're going to now.
I presume you're not going to go spy on what's your name?
Did he want to make a charitable contribution to the GoFundMe for the?
He's not interested.
Did he even believe me?
Does he even think that I am Vukradin?
Do I need to explain it to him?
Well, I mean, you can roll your persuasion, right?
Your persuasion is 17.
You know, he's on the drunk side, right?
And you're so charming and like so convincing that he's like, man, I don't have a lot of money, but he hands you over 10 gold pieces.
Wow, that's pretty generous, actually.
That's a hell of a random nobody.
We need to put that in the correct, that goes in the studio fund.
So that does not go in the regular coffers.
But thank you very much for contributing to the studio fund.
That's awesome.
He goes, he pauses, you know, it's a little bit on the drunk side and goes, like, do I get on, like, is there some kind of like signage for people who contributed to it?
Absolutely.
Yes.
And so.
There's different tiers of giving levels, actually.
10 gold pieces puts you at the premiere or the plus, which was at the plus level.
Yeah, you're not quite at premiere yet.
Yeah, you're at plus level.
10 gold is a lot for a rando.
He's like, you know, he's happy to hear that.
We need his name.
We need to write his name down because we'll have to put it in the program notes.
Yeah, it'd be an extra section.
A year.
I mean, then if you want to be in next year, you'll have to donate again.
But for one year, that's a long time.
Yeah, we call this Patreon.
It's my Patreon.
Exactly.
This is where it comes from.
Patronage.
Okay, I need a name.
All right, let's go get it.
Bob.
No, no, no.
I have all these books with all these names.
Yeah, but we're going to make fun of them.
And you're going to be mad that we're going to make fun of them.
Actually, no, I don't get that mad.
Before we go, should I go around and try to convince other people to contribute to the studio fun?
How much time do we have?
It's like three.
It's like at 3 a.m.
It's like, let's, you got, you got plenty of time.
All right, let's do, let's hit up a few more people.
Let's see how it goes here.
I'll do five more.
One, two, three, four, and five.
Some pretty good rolls there.
25, 26, 25, 17, 17.
All right.
Never below your minimum of 15.
The minimum 17.
Oh, your minimum is 17 now.
It used to be 15, I thought.
It used to be 15.
Yeah, it's gone up.
All right.
So inflation on your persuasion.
We leveled up.
One guy rolled a natural 20 and just looks at you and goes, realizes you're the real Vukradin.
Yeah.
But says, you know, that he's already done his charitable giving for this year.
Okay.
I'm not here to pressure anybody.
Yeah.
The benefits are all on you if you can be at the plus or premiere level.
Like I just like fans.
Right.
And he says, biggest fan, biggest fan.
Oh, bigger than Brewbarry?
Brewbarry is very large.
Do you have a 20-foot reach?
No, he's not that big.
He looks at Brewbarry and goes, no, I'm not that big.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Nobody's as big as Brewbarry.
It's just how.
You know.
So, yeah.
So the third guy is just like, you know, and the fourth person also.
So four of the people all are, you know, enthralled by your, you know, your, your, by your thing.
Yeah.
So, all right.
So one of them is
right.
So there's like these one person's name, Wick, Sabatha, Old Hesp, and Andrell Cass.
Wow.
That's great.
Well, let's add them to the program notes.
And there, I'll just put the names here so that we know.
That's awesome.
Right.
And, you know.
By the way, like the second guy, Wick, you know, is really excited, has no idea who Lefander's death is, you know, and is really into patron of the arts and doesn't really believe you are Vukradin, but doesn't really care if you are or not, Vukradin.
He just thinks it's awesome that you're putting together a music school.
School?
Well, that's what you said.
Studio, right?
School, studio, they're all the same, right?
If you have a studio, it's for training people.
That's just how it goes.
Yeah, and he kind of assumes that.
Yeah.
Sabatha is like, you know, and she's like staring at Brewbarry and giving him the, you know, look over and can't help but comment about how he's committed to the brewbarry look.
Yes.
He is quite bulging, isn't he?
Rippling.
Exactly.
And the last guy you meet is old Hesp.
And you recognize him, or rather, he recognizes you
and says, I remember when you used to play to an empty room.
Yeah.
Did you come?
Did I give you your money back at the end of the day?
Yeah.
Yes, you did.
He said that if I didn't love it, you wouldn't take my, if I didn't give you a 10 out of 10, I wouldn't give you.
I know.
That's how honest I am.
Well, what do you think now?
He pauses.
He goes, Now this is a friggin expensive place to be.
Everybody's got to look cool.
Well, come to the new studio.
It's up and running.
He goes, it doesn't have the look, that feel, that grill.
We're going to get it back.
This is too commercial.
Yeah, yeah, I agree.
It's too commercial.
I mean, Petra's turned this into a money-making operation.
I got to respect her.
She's, you know, she turned.
I mean, I remember when that table he points where, you know, the Brewbarry table was, you know, was not leather and shiny and with a plaque.
And then he goes, and we didn't have this kind of fancy food here.
Okay.
Did we raise a little bit more money?
So you raised 10 little pieces to another 10.
I'll take it.
Sounds good.
All right.
Let's go do some spelunking.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
You're at the third hour.
And what are you casting?
Okay, so tell me what you're casting.
I find familiar.
Dropped it up in the chat a little bit ago.
Okay.
Yeah, we just have to stay within 100 feet.
I'm going to create a little rat.
I see and hear everything the rat hears.
100 feet is pretty close.
Yeah, but you know, we can be like on the other side of walls.
It's not like line of sight 100 feet.
Okay.
There's corners and everywhere.
You know, we can make it work.
All right.
Okay.
So you're at a grill that goes into the, I guess, sewers.
Oh, okay.
A crate.
Yeah.
So it's kind of like aqueduct steps and kind of like thing.
There's whetstone.
There's two crate carriers.
And you can see them dropping down the crates.
All nine of them.
No, yeah, all nine of them.
Okay.
So we want one person to track down the gnome, right?
Crate nine.
Yes.
Also, we want to track the people who dropped them.
So we want to do two things.
Do you want to track that or the gnome?
Like, we can split.
You said you got your high stealth.
Yeah.
If you want, I can track the gnome.
You guys can go do the sewers.
Okay.
Well, I'm tracking the crate.
Which crate?
The ninth crate, the one that doesn't go into Lim, because I'm more concerned about my friend's shady business.
We're not going to follow.
Okay, so you want me to follow them back into the sewers?
That seems pretty dangerous.
One person in this one party member in the sewers.
I see.
All right.
We can send the rat that way then.
You can follow the crate.
All right.
Okay, so what's happening is Valphine, Soma, Brewbarry are tracking the familiar 100 feet behind into the sewers.
Yeah, as it follows the two delivery men back to the sewers.
Yeah, okay.
We say above ground.
Okay, just to be clear.
So what happens is that they just drop these boxes near this grill.
Right.
And they just walk away.
Like they're just walking away.
So what is it that you want to what?
So what this see a bunch of crates being deposited, but you know, what you look at the what you notice about the crates is they clearly don't have the commission harbor mark on them.
Right, meaning they've been smuggled in here somehow.
No, we knew that.
All right, I'm just reminding you.
And, you know, as they're packing them away, one of the carriers stops halfway as he's like leading these crates, looks down into the dark, and then walks away.
Like down at the crates or the yeah, at the grill where the crates are from, where the crates are.
Is your rat chasing the two people?
The rat's going to go whichever way leads to the sewer.
Okay.
So who's so?
Is somebody following these guys, the carriers?
I think this crate was going to go underground.
We were going to send Dave after the Vukradin for top side with the people, right?
So it's got dropped off.
Lim's going to come out and take eight of the crates.
Right.
And she's not going to take a ninth crate.
Vukradin is going to stick around and stealthily wait to see who comes to get to the ninth crate and will track that person.
Oh, these so these are the guys, these guys are going down into the sewer?
I thought they were just walking out.
They're coming from the sewers, yes.
Oh, they came right.
They came up from the sewers.
If you want to go to the sewers, you're going to have to follow them.
Yes, yes.
They're not actually going back into the sewers.
They're walking away.
Well, I think you should still follow them.
Yeah.
So everyone other than Crawford is going to trail these guys, and then Vukradin is going to trail the crate.
Is that right?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll get there.
I'm a little slow.
Okay.
So
they come out of the sewers, they drop the crates, and then they just walk on through town.
Which way?
Right, right.
Yeah, they just kind of look at each other.
So they kind of like act as if they don't know each other and they sort of split up.
That nonchalant whistling.
Oh, if they split up, that's going to make them hard to follow.
You're going to have to use one or split again.
I'd want to roll an insight check to figure out which of them looks like the one in charge relative to each other.
Who's the more senior member?
Oh.
12.
You did not roll one.
Hold on.
And then Bardic inspiration.
All right.
Oh.
So that is a 19.
Let me check off Bardic Inspiration.
Okay, you used the last one.
No more Bardic inspiration until we long rest.
All right.
That was Willie.
Okay.
So there were two guys.
One of them was one of them.
One of them, as I said, like, so you had to put the nine, put the eight crates in what the ninth crate was put on the ledge.
And the guy who put it on the ledge looked down as if he was looking for something and walked away.
So with your other guy, just was stacking the boxes.
I'd follow the guy who paid attention to the ledge.
He knows something's coming out of that thing.
Okay.
All right.
So are you going to they so as they so they split up and they go into different directions.
Which one?
So, you follow, I'm presuming.
Follow the one who's who looked down at the sewers, you know.
All right, who sees more than just grunt work labor?
Right.
Hold on.
Who's uh, who's next to the crate?
Just I want to make sure I know that.
Right.
Okay.
So, I'll stop here first.
And the rest of you are following the carrier.
Yeah.
All right.
I could handle this myself, guys.
You don't trust me.
So, something comes up for it, and it is not a person.
Small, quick, brass and leather, cat-sized, moving with the unhurried, unhurried competence of a thing following instructions.
It takes the crate and goes back down.
Vukradin will pursue stealthily.
All right.
Okay.
This is my concern.
Vukradin ends up going into the sewers now.
Oh, I'll be fine.
One person in the sewers.
All right.
I've got advantage.
Never tell me the odds.
Okay, this is the end of Vukradin.
All right.
Only a one in 400 chance of disaster.
It'll be fine.
All right.
So Denver, the guy you're following goes for, stops at a cook shop that's open at the fourth hour.
Can't be a lot of those.
No, there's not a lot of those.
And he seems to be happily eating it.
By the way, Wade, you have one of the sending stones, and I have the other sending stone.
Ah, good to know.
So we can have little walkie-talkies over.
Yes, we have walkie-talkies.
All right.
He's not eating total soup or anything at this hour, is he?
It's not the Broad Laid Bear.
He's at, of course, he's somewhere else.
Okay.
So are you?
So, by the way, the clock is ticking.
So about 15 minutes have elapsed.
Okay.
I'm just telling you because there's the tide.
That's my point.
Oh, right, right, right.
So do you want to jump him?
He's like, he's like eating his food.
Do you want to walk up to him?
Like, what do you want to do with him?
He's just eating alone.
He's not talking to anybody.
It's late at night.
It's 4 a.m.
You know, the locals there are.
Remember, we promised Lim we're not going to spook her connections.
You promised Lim.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not trying to get her, you know, out of business.
I don't know.
I kind of want to see where he goes next.
I mean, just stopping off for a snack, that doesn't tell us anything.
And spooking him doesn't seem like kosher.
You could walk up to him and talk to him.
I mean, looking at him, Valphine's intuition tells you that he's just what he appears to be: a delivery guy, a delivery guy.
Guy with no knowledge.
Well, we don't know who hired him, though.
Like, what is their route for smuggling?
I think.
I mean, I think we've missed the route at this point.
I think he's just going about his daily business.
Well, he picks up stuff every day.
Right.
Yes.
Like, if you find out where he lives and where he goes, like, maybe you want to see where he is at 2 a.m.
But in order to do that, you need to figure out where he's going to be at 2 a.m.
That sort of thing.
Yeah.
Take multiple nights to stake him out.
Possibly.
Brewbarry will be happy about that.
All right.
We'll stop here.
Make a wisdom saving throw.
Me?
No, I'm talking to Dave.
Okay.
Wisdom save.
I don't think that's going to go very well.
Okay.
You've got advantage.
Not on saves.
Oh.
What happens?
Natural one.
Good times.
Oh, no.
I mean, okay.
There's a passive charm effect or something.
So, what happens is you suddenly become disinterested with where you're going, decide that this is utterly boring and totally not worth your time and start walking away.
You turn into Brewbarry.
Like you get overwhelmed with this confused, like, like confused confusion.
Passive.
A passive confusion effect.
All right.
Awesome.
No, it wasn't a passive confusion effect.
Well, it can't have been cast directly on me.
No, no, no.
It was like an area effect.
Yes, it was an area effect.
So where do I wander off to?
Common Chord?
No, no, not to the Common Chord.
As you walk away, I just need to read one more thing because I took up, made a lot of notes here.
Where is he?
So you see a collection, you see a guy standing in front of you with a bunch of other kind of
like he looks at you funny.
He says, How the hell did you get over here?
I don't know.
Where am I?
He goes, He looks at you and he says, Why?
So you were disinterested in following the tunnel, but you still remember where you were.
You basically decided that this was not the right way to go.
Do you see what I'm saying?
It's not that you got confused.
It's like the whole idea of going down this path seemed like not interesting anymore.
Okay.
So he asked me why I'm here.
Yes.
And then I say, because I'm not over there.
He looks at you funny and goes, roll an insight check.
Oh, yeah, because that's one of my roles.
Why do you have me doing all the roles I'm not good at?
But because you're not trying to convince him with your, well, hold on.
You're supposed to roll your persuasion to start talking to him.
Like he's pressing you and you're just sitting there.
So I'm just like, I was assuming you'd start rolling your persuasion and try to convince him.
Why do I need to convince him of anything?
I'm going to find out what he wants or why he's here.
Well, that's not persuasion.
All right.
Well, I rolled a seven, so go ahead.
You notice nothing about him.
Yeah, I would say so.
All right.
So I guess I want to talk my way out of the situation so that I can reunite with my friends because that's more interesting than the stakeout I was supposed to be doing.
Is that what you're saying?
All right.
Well, no, no, no.
I'm sure I can talk myself out of this.
No, he's not.
That's the thing that the impression you get is he doesn't, he's not like angry at you.
He's like confused as to what are you doing here.
But I don't know what I'm doing here.
Well, you do know that you were looking after the right, yeah.
You do know that.
But why you're specifically there, you don't know.
Oh, well, I wouldn't want to reveal that.
So that's deception.
Yeah, so I just want to say you just fine.
I'll do a deception role.
23.
All right.
And you've successfully convinced him you don't know where you are.
Yeah, there you go.
I'm lost.
I don't know.
I don't know how I got here.
I just long turn.
Should have taken that left at Albuquerque.
He looks at you,
slicks his licks his finger and says, well, that's and so he says, well, this is my territory.
This is your territory.
Yes, this is my territory.
Wow.
Sewers.
Okay.
Did you want me to go?
He goes, I'd want to know why you're in my territory.
Oh, I'm sorry that I got lost.
I'm happy to leave.
Could you point me in the direction of Lim's Cafe?
That's where I want to be headed.
He looks at you funny.
Lim's Cafe?
Yeah.
Huh.
We're friends.
That's interesting.
Why are you?
And he suddenly becomes very interested in the fact that you're friends with Lim.
Yeah.
Okay.
He's like looking at you very kind of like suspiciously now.
He's toying with the idea of like what whether he should do something with you.
But then
he recognizes you somehow.
He goes, Are you that singer?
Exactly.
Lim's a fan.
What are you doing down here, man?
I told you I got lost.
He looks at you and says, Vukradin, you're Vukradin, right?
And one of the guys standing next to him is really smiling and very happy.
He goes, is this really Vukradin?
Do you guys want autographs?
Well, they're like, we'd love some autographs, Mr.
Vukradin.
We can do some autographs, but then I got to be going.
He goes, maybe you can point me in the right direction.
You know what?
We're going to do one better.
We're going to take you there.
All right.
Sounds good.
We don't want you to get lost again, Mr.
We don't want you to get lost again, Mr. Vukradin.
Yeah, exactly.
Lim will be thrilled.
And then he pauses.
You have to know it's very dangerous down here.
Is it?
Yeah, it's dangerous in your territory?
Well, he goes.
I would think you would keep it very, you seem like a very safe kind of individual.
I'm sure he keeps plays ship shape.
He goes, Mr.
Vukradin, I agree with you.
But I have to tell you that the reason I was out here, and I was a little bit concerned when I saw you, and I have to say, I'm very glad that I was able to recognize you.
From, yeah, one of my guys over here tells me that you have a deal with a friend of mine.
At the Common Court?
No, no, at the toe mine.
Mountain Toes.
Oh, yeah.
This is a we're at.
Great.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know you knew him.
Oh, yeah.
He, well, you know, no, it's a.
Yeah, we spent some time in Phandalin.
Yeah.
He, he, he, he said that he had a business relationship with you.
I said that he was full of shit.
No, no, that's true.
That's true.
Yeah, well, they haven't produced very much yet, but they say they're working hard.
He kind of laughs.
Yeah.
That's how I feel about it, too.
He laughs.
And he says, look, look, here's here's a, I manage the tunnels here.
You know, and make sure that.
Oh, you're the tunnel manager.
Yeah, tunnel manager.
So this is your territory, and you have all the tunnels.
Not all the tunnels, but the tunnels in this area.
The tunnels in this area.
Interesting.
Okay.
Right.
There's all I know is that, and so I'm a little bit, you know.
Two months ago, things started to come up the floodline.
Floodline.
Yeah, basically, as he goes, he explains the tunnel that would flood every.
I don't know anything about tunnels, man.
I'm a musician.
He goes, well, I don't know, man.
It's like, I've been having this problem with these tunnels.
I've lost men, so we just don't go there anymore.
Did you need some help with that?
Because we're trying to look for ways to make money.
We have some abilities, me and my friends.
If you need some help, maybe we can help you.
He goes.
And then he starts talking about, well, 25.
You didn't even have to roll for it.
He wants your help.
He really wants my help.
Well, he goes, there's a, well, here's the thing: one of the guys who escaped there said there was some kind of creature that they'd never seen before.
Oh, creature stuff.
It looked like a spider, but it had all the wrong colors.
Okay.
You guys, you would have remembered this from the mine.
The webs it created were all wrong.
They were not, there was something really off about them.
Anyway, we decided.
I have some experience with that.
Oh, well, that's, you know, it.
I mean, and he goes, Mr.
Vukradin, I know this is too much to ask, but could you get me some tickets to the Common Cord?
I can ask.
You know, we have kind of an arm's length relationship with the Common Cord, but I will ask for you.
That's all I can ask for.
All right, let's do some autographs and then we got to be on our way.
All right.
Okay.
So you appear.
All right.
Meanwhile, the rest of you, this guy, you know, after he has his dinner and his lunch and dinner at 4 a.m.
No, no, no, no.
His breakfast heads to what you assume is his place of rest and goes to sleep.
You know where he lives.
He's just a night ship.
So what part of town does he live in?
He lives in the.
I was not anticipating this part of the branch, but that's okay.
How far from the.
I need to pull up the map.
Or put him in the Blue Lake District.
Blue Lake?
Okay.
Or just put a note here.
I mean, we send the rat in.
Just see if I can find any, you know, any odd signs, any receipts, any sort of pay stubs, anything to get a sense.
You know, this guy is just like, he is what he is.
He's just a guy who collects things.
The one thing you will say, though, is that as you're starting to look around, he's making a little bit more money than you just make for.
I mean, that's something to see, right?
He's got nice clothes.
Does he have, you know.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
It's like, you know, you're piecing it together.
Like, somebody who just carries good doesn't go spend money at a restaurant at 4 a.m.
Yeah, he's a little overcompensated for his job.
Yes.
No signs, no.
No, but no marks, no insignias, nothing for the rat to spot.
No, nothing.
No, there's no insignia.
It's just he's a guy who apparently has found a good gig.
Oh, shit.
I want that gig.
So does it look in the middle of the middle?
If you want to run Bronze, it is available as a career wade, but I don't recommend it.
Yeah, it worked well for the Dread Pirate Roberts.
So is he in a house or is he in an apartment?
He's in a place with many rooms.
How about I put it that way?
A hotel.
Okay, so he has a landlord.
Yes, he has a landlord.
Who we could potentially ask questions about him of.
Yeah, absolutely.
But it's middle of the night, huh?
You could wait until the morning, like 7 a.m.
Yeah, it sounds like an SRO type place.
Well, I'm not what an SRO is.
Single room occupancy.
Yeah, that one of those.
Yes.
High-efficiency flat.
Yes, it's a, yeah, that's.
So it's one of those things, right?
It's a high-efficiency flat.
I mean, you know, there's a landlord.
There's a lot of random people in there.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
So he's kind of like looking at you.
You know, he's in his bedroom.
There's a person sitting there.
Obviously, it looks like the person who runs the place.
And you guys just walk up to them or.
Yeah, no, I mean, we can't spook him indirectly.
So we'll just talk to the landlord.
All right.
We just had some questions.
We wanted to know what's it cost to live here.
I think it's the first one we need to know.
She goes, she goes, I don't see many turtles around here.
That's not what I asked.
It's a racist SRO.
Yeah, humans only.
Goodly races only.
No, she's not racist.
She's like, I thought turtles carried their house on their shoulders, so they didn't need a place to stay.
Oh, wow.
No, not racing.
Ah, I see what you think of us.
I can't live in this thing.
It merely protects me.
I actually have a nice cabin out in the woods out by.
Oh, God, where did we start?
Never winter.
Yeah.
Well, outside of it.
I was not in Neverwinter proper.
Yeah, yeah.
So she kind of looked, the guy looks at you and goes, oh, well, I learned a new thing.
I did not know that turtles did not live in their shells.
I guess you're not like turtles.
No, no, we have very, that's kind of slanderous to us.
Suddenly he realizes that he suddenly finally figures out.
He sort of notices Valphine.
And Brewbarry, and he suddenly realizes that maybe this was not the right person to make his commentary.
I'm just asking a question.
Oh, I'm just asking questions.
I see.
Just trying to learn.
That's in questions guy has entered the chat.
Just asking questions.
Look, I'll pretend I didn't hear some of that.
I just want to know what it costs to live here and what kind of people normally stay in a place like this.
You could say I'm looking for a place for my shell sprouts in the future.
He goes, Well, look, you know, I mean, first of all, we don't care.
We're an equal opportunity housing establishment.
You know, we don't.
So progressive.
He goes, it's not about progressive.
It's like, money is money, man.
I don't care who's got it.
I ask every question.
He looks at Valphine and goes, You're a Drow.
Very astute.
I thought Drow didn't like the sunlight.
Oh, I love the sunlight.
Did this guy just come out of like every hour?
But he's not racist.
No, he's race.
I love the sunlight.
He's asking questions.
It's not our duty to educate.
He needs to learn on his own.
He needs to put in the work.
I'll stop here.
I'm glad I'm not there to witness it.
Yes.
Really, I get all to you on the sending stones.
Don't worry.
Yeah, that's right.
Hello to this guy.
So, yeah, you just take money.
You don't ask questions.
So you don't know anything about your tenants.
You don't know about that.
Oh, how do we know that?
KYC laws in here.
He goes, look, this is one of these.
This is a kind of place where you better have some cash up front to stay.
So it turns out it's kind of like not the kind of place where someone who's a day laborer would live.
Yeah, it seems odd.
You never do any sort of background check?
You never make sure that people have the gold that they claim they're going to have after a month, you know?
No, he's like, he goes, I don't scry on my customers.
I don't believe that.
Given the racism you presume, I'm sure you scry on certain ones of them, don't you?
Yeah, he noticed Brewbarry's pecs.
Just jiggling about.
At this point, he's going like, look, look, I don't want any trouble.
If you want a place to stay here, I'll give you a discount.
Really, we just want to know about one of your tenants.
All right.
We ask him about the gentleman we've followed back here.
Yeah.
He goes, You mean Denvar?
Denvar.
Yeah.
That's more than we came with.
We got a name.
Got a name.
Denvar.
Denver.
It's going on the quest tracker.
Denvar, Colorado.
Denvar.
You will soon.
Yes, yes.
We mean Denvar.
Denvar.
He dropped something last night.
We saw him skulking about in the alleyway.
It's super late at night, and he dropped a little pouch.
We'd like to return it to him.
Making a delivery.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, there was one detail I forgot to tell you.
Oh.
Right.
Every he's got the whole world.
He's got chits, like, you know, say like his the job, right?
Yeah, see, this is what the rat was going in looking for.
Yeah, I forgot, I forgot, I've like I had to put my notes together, right?
So, um, you know, so this is, you know, he has his chits to tell him he does the job, this would be the, and he's got seven, ten days of them in order.
Each one of them reads nine crates, third hour, eight up, one down.
Right?
And there's a weekly settlement.
Third up, one down.
Right.
Eight up, one down.
So basically.
Oh, eight up.
Sorry.
Okay.
Eight up, one down.
Eight up, yeah.
One down.
There's a client reference, a house mark, and no name anywhere on any of them.
And all his deliveries, 100% of his delivery chits are the same.
They're all this one thing.
He literally has one job.
Yeah.
It is.
Wow.
Yeah, no, that's not suspicious.
Right.
So it's like somebody, it's like, and there's all they all look settled, right?
They have the checks on them, whatever.
Right, right.
Stamp of payment.
But no, nothing identifiable on them other than just they clearly seem to be related to this one contract.
Yes.
Okay.
Denvar.
Yes.
All right.
So, yeah, does the racist establishment owner have any information on Denvar beyond the name?
Oh, one thing you'd landlord's name.
Uncle Tom.
Perfect.
I love it.
No.
Done.
That's just.
I on the nose, man.
A little bit too on the nose.
Okay.
So,
all right.
Okay.
So, so, sorry, so he he's so there's like there's there's a whole bunch of these.
And one of the things you do notice is that today, later in the day, he is the one that one of the chits has not been settled.
So, like, there's seven, but the seventh one has not been paid for.
And so, that was the one that he just presumably delivered.
Yeah, so I guess we have reason to follow him once he wakes up, don't we?
Yes.
Yeah, that's going to go collect payment.
Yeah, I assume he needs to be able to afford a place like this.
Yeah, he needs the money pretty quick.
In fact, we could ask the landlord: you know, is Denvar settled up on his bills?
Denvar.
Well, he goes, he owes me some money today.
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay.
All right.
If he doesn't pay up today.
Yeah, so he's motivated.
Be it tomorrow.
You know, he's just sleeping in his room right now, right?
Like, yeah.
Well, I mean, he's got till the end of the day.
And he's a good customer.
He's quiet.
He doesn't bother anybody.
I'll bet.
Good guy, huh?
Yeah, totally good guy.
You don't think he's a serial killer or anything?
He looks at you again, Tortal, wearing with staff of Meryl, you know, Valphine in her white armor and glowing eyes, and Halberd and his Brewbarry with his Halberd, and looks and goes, Well, should I be worried?
You never know with these types.
You never know.
All right.
Can we worry about him?
I think we can let Uncle Tom off the hook.
Right.
So Uncle Tom's kind of like, you know, I just want you to know.
I mean, we're always.
And if you've got now that I know that pauses, he's trying to like really hard.
So Soma, right?
You introduced yourself at some point.
Yes, yes, I definitely did.
He goes, Soma, look, now that I know that turtles are looking for housing, perhaps you could tell me, like, what makes a good turtle room?
Oh, a nice hearth, you know, plenty of water.
Usually near a body of water is nice.
All turtles are the same, right?
Yes, I speak for all tortoises.
The Jesse Jackson of Tortles.
I was giving you an opportunity to troll the guy, but Soma doesn't troll.
No, Soma does not.
Snow does not.
Soma's earnest.
All right.
Okay.
So a few hours later, he wakes up.
And I assume I have to recast my rat at some point.
Yes.
I don't think it lasts forever.
Let me just burn another slot.
You guys are just giving me updates on the Sunday.
So at this point, I should probably join you, right?
It's been a few hours.
Yeah, yeah, we can have you come along.
I probably am with you now.
Yeah.
We can tell you about Denver.
I'm going to tell you about the local were rat mafia.
Yeah, that's just were rats all over, isn't it?
Expect them to be such a big player.
We just got to clear out these spiders, and it's more money for the studio.
This is great.
Finally, a business opportunity.
Fair trade.
All right.
Okay.
Now I know.
All right.
You show up
and you.
Okay.
So you go to the stone.
He goes to a stone wall.
He opens up and you see that he looks around, trying to be as discreet as possible.
To dead drop.
He picks up.
He opens it, pulls a stone, and he grabs a bag and he closes the bag.
Just a bare stone wall, like on the edge of the.
It's a stone that backs into a building, right?
So it's like, right?
And so it backs into a building.
Is it like a two-way?
It's like
a doctor's office window, right?
Like where you put it in on one side and close the door, and then they'd have to go.
We'd have to go inspect it.
Yeah, you'd have to go inspect it.
All right.
Well, it's, yeah.
I mean, it's effectively a dead drop.
So like, we should let him go and just inspect at this point.
Yeah.
I mean, Barring coming back the next evening before he leaves his house, but we don't know exactly how early he has to leave to make these to drops.
So it's probably a Denver might be a dead end.
All right.
I have all the wall.
All right, so you go to the wall, right?
Valphine, you want to do your internet perception?
You mean like on him or on the wall?
On the wall.
I'm going to look at him just before he goes.
He looks at the chip and he smiles.
He's please.
You got it.
Okay.
He got his money.
Hey, Day!
Going to the casino.
Yeah.
Take a little look then at the rock.
What you notice is that the rock, I mean, basically, it's a two-way rock, right?
Somebody, you don't know if the person who puts it in was on the other side of the rock or on this side.
It was in the house or not in the house, so you'd have to go into the house to check it out.
Oh, okay.
Well, let's loop around.
Don't tell him it's stone or is it earth or it's a stone dwelling.
It's a stone dwelling.
It's raw, you know, built out of stone.
Trying to think we have something that can help us without going into the house.
I mean, we have lulled earth, but I know you won't.
It's not earth, it's stone.
Let's just quickly look around the house and see what it is.
It's gotta be the outside of the house.
Yeah, it's gotta be a Margaster residence or something like that.
No, it's not a shop.
You don't think that's what I'm cautioning.
Is it residence or a shop?
Give me one second.
I'm on the fly coming up with this shit.
Okay.
So I need to make up my mind.
You didn't plan for this eventuality?
No.
Teasing.
All right.
As you walk around, you realize that the house you've landed on is actually a tavern.
Great.
The house of a thousand faces.
So many taverns.
Yeah.
You can just walk right in.
Are they open?
Yeah.
It is early in the morning, but no, they are in fact open.
I mean, somebody's obviously in there paying off shady debts.
What?
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
We can hit the tavern.
I mean, it's early, but why not?
Five o'clock somewhere.
Sure, Brewbarry is all for it.
All right.
I just, what did I call it?
I gave it a name.
The House of a Thousand Faces.
All right.
Let me just make sure it's not hidden.
The House of a Thousand Faces.
There we go.
Oh, so I do have an idea of how we can investigate this without going inside, which is the knock spell.
So we could open our side and we can cast knock on the other side.
Do you want to try to do that or do you want to just go inside the tavern?
I assume someone would just go inside.
She's not exactly a magic wielder or familiar with all that.
Sorry, how does you use knock to open up the two-way dead drop stuff or what?
Yeah, like, right, we can't open the other side of the, we can't physically open the other side of the two-way hole, but we could, I think we could magically open it if we wanted to do that.
I mean, if you, if you propose that, yeah, I think that's worth it.
And then we could look in and see what room are we looking at to try to find the right room, or we could even send one of your rats in there to look around.
I like that combo.
I have a different strategy, which is we go in there and offer them this is proposal.
Yeah, Vukradin could play.
Burger booking agency.
Actually, you know, getting backstage in there would, you know, you'd have access to staff-only areas where you could, you know, do your music prep and by music prep.
There you go.
We could cast two spells, or we could have an extended contract process and several performance roles and hours of time.
I do like to perform, though.
Yeah, see, I mean, these are tough choices.
Let's do both.
Porque no los dos.
Exactly.
Why not?
I'll fire off another.
We'll have to ask the DM if it works.
But the idea is that we open our side of the hole.
We cast knock on the other side of the hole, hopefully opening it, and then send the rat, the familiar rat, through to look around and what the room on the other side.
Did you get all that?
Yeah, I did.
Okay.
Just a simple strategy.
Yeah.
All right.
That's what you're doing.
What are the other, what is everybody else doing?
Are you all like doing that together?
Before we go inside, we're all together.
Yeah, we want to at least not walk in completely blind.
All right.
So maybe Brewbarry runs off and gets, you know, just goes in and orders beer without waiting for us, but I don't know.
Brewbarry, tavern.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't think we could kick him away into the tavern.
That's a great way for trying to solve the puzzle.
Brewbarry's already in the tavern.
Yeah, he was born in the tavern.
He's down.
He's actually at this point.
Actually, to be fair, Brewbarry has heard about this tavern for some time.
And when he was first in Neverwinter, he could never get there because he never had the money.
Oh, there you go.
It's more of a high-end establishment.
He was more of a Common Cord slum, and this was a high-end establishment.
Yeah, I mean, you know, and he'd heard about this place.
He's a man of class now.
He can buy his way into high society.
I do have one question about our fame, though.
Sorry, it's a little bit off topic, but do we know how we became so famous?
Or is that a mystery for us to be solving?
You do not know how you became.
Yeah, I thought so.
Okay.
Isn't it obvious?
Yes.
It's the quality of your talent.
It definitely is not.
But of course, there is a force behind the thing that is some groups are maneuvering to their advantage for some reason.
Yes.
All right.
Okay.
So you send in the rat.
The rat like sneaks around.
So knock does work on the stone wall thing.
Okay.
Yeah, it does work on it.
And as the rat is looking around, you realize that this is the back office of the it looks like a back office.
No windows, no nothing.
The rat looks around and notices a symbol of the harpers.
So this is a harper harper.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
So is it like a storage room or like one of the, you know, think of a spike desk, papers, kind of things like that.
Desk papers.
Supplies.
Well, you wouldn't steal anything, so yes.
No, no, it's just a rat.
No, they're right.
I can't carry anything.
Vukradin wouldn't steal anything.
No.
No, no, he's a man.
He definitely wouldn't steal anything.
I know, just every time I with other parties, I have to be thoughtful because the next thing is they're going to go steal everything.
He can't see what the rat's doing, though.
He only has to trust my word for it.
Yeah, sorry.
But no, it looks like HQ for the Harpers, the local Harpers.
Harper, so that's weird.
The Harpers are smuggling?
Well, the Harpspers aren't.
Are the Harper smuggling or are they arranging for that ninth crate?
Well, I mean, clearly that ninth crate is some amount of smuggling because it's being, you know, indirectly delivered.
So, yes, the Harpers are smuggling in some capacity.
Yes.
Oh, just want to remind you: the Harpers in my campaign world are not good people.
Oh, okay.
There's no, the only good people are the Order of the Gauntlet.
Debatable.
They're reformed.
Why?
Well, they had that whole thing with the barbarians, you know.
Well, that was that.
They were misled by their political masters.
Exactly.
That's what I'm saying.
They're reformed now.
Right.
And so they've now rejected those political masters.
Exactly.
They're the reformed Order of the Gauntlet.
Yes.
And they recognize that they were used by powerful forces.
And now they're all about, you know, the little guy.
Truth, justice, and the American way.
Oh, no.
Different comic book.
All right.
It's .
Yeah, just to give you guys shoes.
So it's a comfortable tavern.
It's got mirrors and mannequins and antiquated fashions, lush couches, right?
Mannequins in it, anyway.
Lush couches, a fire that actually draws.
It's kind of like a high-end place, and the Blue Lake District is sort of a low-end place.
There's something off about it.
And as for where the rat was, it wasn't in the first floor, but it kind of went.
Anyway, it was in the basement level.
Basement level.
Went down.
All right.
Okay.
So Brewbarry walks in, and we'll just, you guys know that it's a Harper.
Yeah.
It's a good place as any to leave it.
It's as good a place as any place to leave it.
So you've arrived in the Harper establishment in the Blue Lake District.
Okay.
And I guess, and we have the information so that at any time we can go face this spider infestation in the sewers and try to clear it out for the weir rat mafia.
Well, you have to go and find the weird rat mafia again.
Yes.
Well, we talked to them and we agreed we'd do this job for them.
So I'm assuming they gave us the necessary information to do the deal.
Yes, yes, they did.
Okay.
Cool.
Maybe we could do that next time.
We haven't had a combat in like.
Well, I know.
I had three combat months since we had a combat.
Dude, I had like three combats set up, but like you guys went in a completely different drink.
It went to left.
What?
What'd you say, Gary?
We went to left field.
Yes, you went into left field, but it's okay.
Okay, so the house of a thousand faces.
We got to third base.
Right.
You went through the sewers over here.
I just need to put a need to put a marker saying there's a sewer entrance over here.
Sewer entrance.
So I don't forget.
Sewer.
You won't forget.
All right.
Okay.
Sewer entrance.
All right.
So the party is at the House of the Thousand Faces, and we'll continue next week.
Yeah.
Have a good week, y'all.
Have a good week.
I had fun today.
I hope you guys did.
Oh, no, it's fun.
Bye-bye.
All right, man.
Take care.